Guide to the William L. Mertz transportation collection, 1955-1990
George Mason University Libraries
- William L. Mertz transportation collection
  - The History and Development of Road Building in the United States [address at the Annual Convention of the American Society of Civil Engineers] October 6, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Memorandum from Mr. M.L. Ramsay to R.E. Royall with attachment - Notebook 7 December 24,1942 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence from Howard H. Baker, JR, and Jennings Randolph to William t. Coleman [re:draft guidelines on planning assistance and guidance] April 23, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence from William T. Coleman to Sterling Tucker [re: concerns about new policies]-Notebook 7 December 1, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Memorandum: Section 134 -- 1962 Highway Act Transportation Planning Group - Notebook 7 June 22, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Memorandum: An evaluation of Urban Transportation Planning - Notebook 7 May 24, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence from Robert E. Jones to Norbert T Tiemann {re: proposed regulations]- Notebook 7 March 28, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - The 1973 Highway Act (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence from William T. Coleman to Gov. Mills E. Godwin [re: concern over planning assistance and standards] - Notebook 7 April 9, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence from Norbert T. Tiemann to Grant Bastian [re;regulations]- Notebook 7 April 2, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence from J.R. Coupal to Robert E. Jones - Notebook 7 September 3, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - The FWHA - UMTA Relationship - Notebook 7 circa 1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Letter from Henrik E. Stafseth to Norbert Tiemann - Notebook 7 November 12, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence from William T. Coleman to Senator Howard H. Baker September 30, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence from William T. Coleman to John C. Roberts May 3, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - The national system of interstate Highways [presented to Fall Meeting of the American Society of civil Engineers]- Notebook 7 March 17, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Post-war Plans for express highways in Urban areas- Notebook 7 November 3, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - The New Federal highway Program - Notebook 9 [National conference on Planning] May 13, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Highways and the National Defense [AASHO] September 16, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Congress Considers Road Legislation - Notebook 9 [American Highways] January, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - The American Automobile Association - Notebook 9 November 17, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Defenseless Highways Defended Notebook 9 [W. C. Markham, AASHO] (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Highway Program for the United States - Notebook 9 [American Petroleum Industries Committee] November 13, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Notebook 9 - National Road Building Through State-Federal Cooperation [25th Annual Meeting of AASHO] October 10, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Notebook 9 - Superhighways; John t. Flynn [Economics] February 9, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Federal Participation in Road Construction - Notebook 9 [John Carmody, AASHO 25th Anniversary Meeting] October 1939 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - The development of Primary roads During the Next Quarter Century - Notebook 9 [Frank T. Sheets AASHO] October 1939 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Congress Felicitate the Association; Delegates Bring Home Words of Congratulations - Notebook 9 October, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Annual Convention Address [AASHO] October 1939 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Where Did the One Percent Come from? [A description of the Federal policy regarding the portion of roads to be included in the inter-state highway system.] (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Toll Roads and Free Roads: a Review of the Final Report - Notebook 9 April, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Our Cities: their Role in the National Economy - Notebook 9 1937 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Review of the BPR Drafts of the Toll Roads and Free Roads - Notebook 9 [Description of Differences between a memorandum from mr. Fairbanks (BPR) the President's message to Congress.] 1939 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Looking Toward the Future [AASHO] December 7, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - MacDonald Tells Me What He Saw in Europe. The Need for Fact in Highway Planning - Notebook 9 [AAA}] November 20, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - What Happened to the Highway Program During the Depression (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Superhighway Legislation - Notebook 9 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - the Origins of the Interstate System - Notebook 9 [FDR's Views] (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - The Earliest Roots of the Interstate System - Notebook 9 [1897] (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Special Roads Reserved for Motor Traffic - Notebook 9 [The Permanent International association of Road Congresses] September, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Street and Highway Accidents - Notebook 9 [Journal of American Insurance] August, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - The Bragdon Committee [cont'd] - Notebook 8 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Address Clifford Davis [to 41st Annual Meeting AASHO] - Notebook 9 December 6, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - address Gore, Albert- Notebook 9 [41st annual meeting AASHO] December 6, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - [AASHO] President's Annual Address - Notebook 9 October 9, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - What Next for the Highway Official After the Authorization of an Enlarged Federal Aid Program - Notebook 9 October, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Statement of Senator Harry F. Byrd - Notebook 9 [Congressional record] June 1955 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Address McGregor, J. Harry - Notebook 9 [40th Annual Meeting AASHO] November 9, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - [AASHO] President's Annual Address - Notebook 9 November 9, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Policy Address [Policy Statement Adopted by AASHO] November 8, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Commissioners [Commissioner of Public Roads] Annual Address - Notebook 9 [40th annual meeting AASHO] November 9, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Address [40th Annual Meeting AASHO] Dondero, George A. - Notebook 9 November 9, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - [AASHO] President's Annual Address - Notebook 9 [contents duplicate that of folder 8] November 9, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Adequate Highways for a Prosperous America [address by A. E. Johnson to Associated General Contractors of America] March 3, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Address, Dempsey, John J., - Notebook 9 [39th Annual meeting AASHO] December 10, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - What's Going on in Public Roads - Notebook 9 November 10, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - [AASHO] President's Address November 10, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Six Suggestions for Safer Highways -Notebook 9 [Senator Francis Case} November 10, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Better Roads for the United States - Notebook 9 [George A. Dondero] November 10, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - National Highway Study - Notebook 9 [Congressional Hearings] April and May 1953 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Better Roads for the United States - Notebook 9 [George A. Dondero address to AASHO] November 10, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - National Highway Study - Notebook 9 [Congressional Hearings][Contents duplicate contents of folder 19] April and May 1953 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - [AASHO] President's Annual Address December 10, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Address Senator L. Holland - Notebook 9 December 10, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - A Choice of Guides - Notebook 9 [MacDonald address to AASHO] December 10, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Statement of the 1952 Policy for Highways Adopted by AASHO - Notebook 9 1952 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report of the Secretary [AASHO] for 1951 [published in American Highways] January 1952 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Critical Aspects of the Current Highway Program [MacDonald address to AASHO] -Notebook 9 December 23, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Relation of the Highway Program to the National Economy [MacDonald address to AASHO] December 4,1950 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - A Review of Highway Policies -Notebook 9 [ MacDonald's Address to Southeastern ASHO] October 5, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Let's Face It - Notebook 9 [editorial from American Highways] October 1950 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - The Interstate System in Urban Areas - Notebook 9 [MacDonald's address to National Citizens Conference on Planning] May 16, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - A New Look at the Federal -Aid Program [MacDonald's address to the American Road Builder's Association] March 6, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Progress of New Federal-Aid Legislation - Notebook 9 April 1950 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Resolutions Adopted by AASHO - 36th Annual Meeting - Notebook 9 January 1950 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Statement of 1950 Policy for Federal-Aid for Highways adopted by the AASHO - Notebook 9 October 1949 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - The Inadequacies of Our Present Highway Transportation Facilities - Notebook 9 [MacDonald address to the American Road builders Association] November 8, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Status and Relative Progress of the Federal-Aid Highway Program - Notebook 9 [MacDonald address to the AASHO] October 11, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Annual Address (1948) - Notebook 9 [H.R. Baldock, AASHO] September 1948 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Annual Address - Notebook 9 [C. W. Phillips, AASHO] September 22-26, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - The Case for Urban Expressways - Notebook 9 [MacDonald quoted in American City Magazine] June 1947 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Toll Roads - Response to the New Hampshire Sunday News - Notebook 9 April 22, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Highway Construction Program - Notebook 9 [MacDonald's address to the Associated General Contractors] January 27, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Your Highway Program - Notebook 9 [Congressman J. W. Robinson address to AASHO] December 17, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - The Highway Improvement Program In Relationship to the Conventional Public Works Concept - Notebook 9 [MacDonald's Address to ASSHO] December 17-20 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Looking ahead in Highway Legislation - Notebook 9 [Congressman J. W. Robinson address to AASHO] April 1946 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Highway Development Under the New Legislation - Notebook 9 [AASHO meeting] January 30, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - [AASHO] President's address to the Convention - Notebook 9 January 1946 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Highway and Related Legislation Introduced in the 79th Congress - Notebook 9 July 1945 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Analyzing Transportation Needs of Urban Areas - A New Technique - Notebook 9 [A summary of 3 speeches delivered by MacDonald] November 3, 1944; November 28, 1945; and January 11,1945 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - An Editorial - Notebook 9 [American Highways] January 1950 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Summary of Testimony on H.R. 2426 - a Proposed Amendment to the Federal-aid Road Act - Notebook 9 April and May 1944 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Testimony of Highway Officials on HR 2426 - Notebook 9 [Hadden, MacDonald and Purcell] April 1944 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Preparing for the Postwar Highway Program - Notebook 9 [MacDonald's address to Association of General Contractors] February 7, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - President's message to the Congress Recommending 34,000 mile Interregional Highway System - Notebook 9 January 1944 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Public Works Planning in War and Peace - Notebook 9 [Major General Phillip Fleming] January 1944 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Proposed Interregional Highway System as it Affects Cities - Notebook 9 [91st Annual Meeting American Society of Civil Engineers] January 21, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Looking Forward - Notebook 9 [ US Congressman J. W. Robinson] January 1944 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Address by Congressman James Mott] Before the 29th Annual Meeting [of AASHO] - Notebook 9 December 1-3, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Future Highway Program Notebook 9 [Address by MacDonald at Annual Meeting of ASSHO] December 2, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Post War Problems Notebook 9 [Congressman Jesse Wolcott] 1944 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Annual Convention Address [AASHO President Brady Gentry] 1943 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Legislation Passed by the U.S. Congress July 7, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Public Building to Come Notebook 9 [Address by Robert Moses to Conference of Highway Officials of the North Atlantic States] July, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Post-War Legislation - Notebook 9 [Address by Congressman J.W. Robinson to the American Road Builders' Association] October, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Post-war Highways - Notebook 9 [A Forecast of Conditions and What We Should Prepare For by G. Donald Kennedy] April, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Transcript of Informal Remarks of Thomas H. MacDonald Before the annual Meeting of the association of Highway Officials of North Atlantic States - Notebook 9 February 18, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Federal - State Road Building Plan vs. Complete National Control [Address by Fred R. White to AASHO] January, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - War's Challenge to Highway administrators - Notebook 9 Address by MacDonald to AASHO] December 7, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - How Do We Go From Here - Notebook 9 [Address by W.C. Markham to AASHO] December 1942 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - The Essential Relationship of Highway Transport to the National Security - Notebook 9 February 26, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - The Indispensable Quality of Highways to the National Defense [Address by MacDonald to AASHO] September 29, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - The Federal-Aid Highway System: a Definite Plan for a System of Roads - Notebook 11 [Article by MacDonald in monthly bulletin of the National Sand and Gravel Producers] May, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Radio Speech - Notebook 11 [[MacDonald] 1923 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - The Relation of Good Roads to the Livestock Industry - Notebook 11 [MacDonald at International Livestock Show] 1923 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Federal Aid Road Work [MacDonald Article in AAA Yearbook] 1923 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Special Roads Reserved for Motor Traffic- Notebook 11 [Address by MacDonald to International Association of Road Congresses September, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Street and Highway Accidents - Notebook 11 [Journal of American Insurance] August, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - The Economy of issuing Bonds to Build Surfaced Roads - Notebook 11 May, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 1925 Highway Developments - Notebook 11 [Manufacturer Record] January 1926 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Our International Relations As Shown By the Pan American Road Congress at Buenos Aires - Notebook 11 November 19, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Highway Research in Ohio - Notebook 11 September 1923 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Commercial Vehicles on Free Highways - Notebook 11 July, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Building a System of National Roads Through Federal-Aid - Notebook 11 January 5-9, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Correlating State and national Highway Programs January 23, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Financial Value of Highway Research - Notebook 11 [address to Highway Research Board] December 4-5, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - The Urgent Necessity for Uniform Traffic Laws and Public Safety Devices - Notebook 11 [MacDonald address to AASHO] November 17-20, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - The Financing of Highways - Notebook 11 November, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Modern Road Construction for Public Parks October 7,1924 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - The Future of American Roads - Notebook 11 [MacDonald article in The Military Engineer] May/June 1924 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - General Economics Underlying the Highway - Notebook 11 [MacDonald Address to World Transport Congress] May 23, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Highway Improvement: Continuing Business - Notebook 11 [American Road Builders Association ] January 14-18,1924 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Federal and State Policies in the Constriction of the Federal Aid Highway System [AASHO meeting] December 3-6, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - The Objectives of Highway Research - Notebook 11 [Advisory Board of Highway Research] November 8, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Federal Aid Facts and Figures April,1922 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - The Future of Road building April 1922 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - highway transport - A Field for Engineers - Notebook 11 March 1922 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - The National Automobile Chamber of Commerce - Notebook 11 March 1, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - The Federal Highway Act - Notebook 11 [Farm and Fireside magazine] February, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Highway Transportation - Notebook 11 [American Society of Civil Engineers] January 20, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - The Highway Outlook - Notebook 11 [American Road builders Association] January 16-20 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Resume of Cooperative Road Improvement and Future Policies - Notebook 11 [AASHO] December 5-8, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - The Problems to be Studied - Notebook 11 [Conference on Highway and Highway Transport Education] 10/10/21 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - The Measure of Accomplishment - Notebook 11 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Rural Transportation May 18, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Address in Connection With the Highway Short Course - Notebook 11 February 21, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Our National Highway Problems - Notebook 11 [Address before Good Roads Convention of American Road builders] February 9, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - What Has Been Accomplished Under Federal Aid ? - Notebook 11 [AASHO] December 14, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Highway Engineering Research - Notebook 11 [Meeting of Land Grant College Association] October 20, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Address Before New York Institute of Consulting Engineers - Notebook 11 October 13, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - address Before North Carolina Good Roads - Notebook 11 June 17, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Highway Engineering - Notebook 11 [Iowa Semi-Centennial] June 8, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Address Before Organizing Conference of Engineers - Notebook 11 June 3 and 4, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - The Widening Field for Engineers in Highway Improvement and Their training For this Field - Notebook 11 [Conference on Highway Engineering Education] May 14, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - The History of the Planning Process - Notebook 10 October 21, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - American Highway [Magazine] Excerpts - Notebook 10 1957 - 1963 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - American Hight [Magazine] Excerpts - Notebook 10 1964 - 1972 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - American Hight [Magazine] Excerpts - Notebook 10 1972 - 1973 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Lessons Learned in Washington, D.C. - Notebook 10 [Highway User Quarterly Fall] (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Newspaper Clips - Notebook 10 1962 - 1963 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - House Hearings on Implementation of Section 134, June 1963 - Notebook 10 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Hearings on the 1962 Highways Act - Notebook 10 April and May 1962 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - American Highways and Transportation Monthly March 1974 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Address by C.D. Curtis to AASHO- Notebook 9 12/6/55 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Federal Highway Administrator Selected- Notebook 9 [Editorial American Highways Magazine] October, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Presentation of the Bartlett Award to William Randolf Hearst 1/12/56 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Highway Administration in the United States of North America - Notebook 9[ address to Pan American Congress of Highways] October 1925 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Federal Funds for Highway and Grade Crossing Work in Ohio - Notebook 11 September 1935 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Public Works Highway Progress - Notebook 11 [New York Times 8/4/35 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Broadening the Highway Program - Notebook 11 [American Address to Road builders Association 1/22/35 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Paper Presented at the Annual Meeting of AASHO - Notebook 11 [ "A milestone speech"] 11/12/34 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Road Building Employment, A Four year Record - Notebook 11 [Contractors and Engineers Monthly] 12/34 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - The Need for Facts in Highway Planning - Notebook 11 1934 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Federal Highway Progress - Notebook 11 [The American Civic Annual] 5/9/34 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Address to the Mississippi Valley Highway Conference - Notebook 11 2/2/34 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Summary of Federal Highway Progress - Notebook 11 [American Road builders Association] 1/22/34 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Looking Forward in Highway Construction - Notebook 11 [Contractors and Engineers Monthly] 1/34 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Federal Direction of Programming and Engineering of Emergency Road Work - Notebook 11 12/16/33 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Tax Payments by the Motor Vehicle - Notebook 11 [address to The Highway Research Board] 12/7/33 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - The Highway Recovery Program - Notebook 11 [AASHO] 10/9/33 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - What Highways Mean in the Economic and Social Life of the United States - Notebook 11 1/19/33 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Economic Factors in the Low Cost Road Program - Notebook 11 12/6/32 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Making Public Roads Pay - Notebook 11 [Bus Transportation] 12/32 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Growing Transportation Problems of the Highway - Notebook 11 [Engineering News Record] December 1932 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - The Building of Minnesota's State Highways - Notebook 11 10/6/32 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Legislative Regulation of Motor Vehicles and Its Effects on Their Design and Operation - Notebook 11 10/5/32 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Address to Eastern Conference of Motor Vehicle Commissioners - Notebook 11 5/6/32 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Road Services for Communities Not on the State Road System - Notebook 11 2/18/32 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Adjusting the Highway Viewpoint to 1932 Conditions - Notebook 11 [American Road builders Association] 1/11/32 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Federal Aid Highways and Their Future - Notebook 11 [Herald Tribune] 12/1931 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Review and Forecast of Public Roads Problems 12/1931 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Current Phases of Highway Building and Maintenance - Notebook 11 [AASHO] 9/21/31 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Relation of the Bureau of Public Roads to the Automotive Industry - Notebook 11 6/1931 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Highways and Railroads - Notebook 11 [The Scientific American] April 1931 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Road Building a Major Employment Agency - Notebook 11 [American Highways] April 1931 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Highway Finance - Notebook 11 3/5/31 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Highway Building With a Particular Reference to [Federal] Employment Program - Notebook 11 [Annual Meeting American Road Builder's Association] 1/12/31 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Roadside Improvement - Notebook 11 [The American Civic Annual] 1930 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Highway Engineering in the United States - Notebook 11 [History] 1930 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - The Practical Application of Highway Transport Surveys to a State Highway System - Notebook 11 [AASHO] 11/17/30 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Bureau of Public Roads - Notebook 11 [inclusion of agricultural concerns] 4/30 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - The Mount Vernon Memorial Highway - Notebook 11 6/15/30 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Highways and Airways - Notebook 11 6/30 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Prequalification of Bidders Benefits Public- Notebook 11 4/30 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Farm to Market Roads - Notebook 11 1/18/30 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Activities of the Bureau of Public Roads in 1928 and 1929 - Notebook 11 [prepared for the New York Journal of Commerce (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - The Evolution of Highway Financing - Notebook 11 [Engineering News Record] 12/23/29 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Financing Highways - Notebook 11 [AASHO] 11/12/29 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Some Highway Questions of the Moment - Notebook 11 [Talk at Second Pan-American Highway Congress] 9/12/29 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - A Nation's Highways - Notebook 11 [Cordoba Argentina] 9/9/29 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - The Highways Turn to Beauty - Notebook 11 4/1/29 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Address at the American Road Builders' Banquet - Notebook 11 1/16/29 (Box 10, Folder 45)